One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Just remember that it was you who cast suspicion on my crew.
Hatırlatırım, tayfamdan şüphe eden sendin.
Without mutual trust, we won't have each other's backs when fighting for our lives!
Aramızda güven yoksa, can derdine düştüğümüzde birbirimizi koruyamayız!
Sparks of Rebellion
İsyan Kıvılcımları
Traf was fuming when he left!
Trao ayrılırken çok öfkeliydi!
Who knows if he'll come back.
Geri dönüp dönmeyeceği meçhul.
Shinobu went too far saying all that crap!
Shinobu saçmaladı ve çok ileri gitti!
You do understand what set her off, right?
Onu neyin delirttiğini anlamadın mı?
Kaido invaded her country and laid waste to everything she had ever known,
Kaido ülkesini işgal edip tüm hayatını harabeye çevirdi,
but she endured it for twenty years while waiting for the moment to fight back.
ama o savaşacağı günü bekleyerek yirmi yıl sabretti.
Whatever. Even if Bepo and the others had blabbed about the plan, I wouldn't blame them.
Neyse ne. Planı, Bepo ve diğerleri öttüyse bile bunun için onları suçlayamam.
Sure, I mean, you'd have talked.
Elbette, sen de aynısını yapardın.
I can say the same about you!
Aynaya bak önce!
Torture, huh?
İşkence, ha?
I'd last three seconds.
Üç saniye dayanırdım.
Hold out longer, will you?!
Zahmet olmasın!
Get outta here!
Defolun lan!
I have no business with any of you damn peasants!
Siz lanet köylülerin hiçbiriyle işim yok!
What's going on? An angry shout seems out of place in Ebisu Town.
Neler oluyor? Ebisu'da öfkeli bir bağırış duymak çok garip.
You there, old bean-washing monster granny!
Ahaa, azuki baba* geldi!
Stop it!
Kes be!
They're new here. They arrived yesterday after fleeing the capital.
Kasabamızın yeni sakinleri. Dün, başkentten kovuldular.
What are you looking at?!
Neye bakıyorsunuz lan?!
Get outta here, punks!
Defolun, bücürler!
They fled the capital?
Kovuldular mı?
Yeah.
Evet.
Only those who produce wealth and show loyalty to the shogun can live in the Flower Capital.
Çiçek Başkenti'nde yalnızca zenginlik üreten ve şoguna sadakat gösterenler yaşayabilir.
I heard those men were doing some pretty scummy things.
Onların epey aşağılık şeyler yaptığını duydum.
First,
Öncelikle...
we have Bungo the flunkey.
...dalkavuk Bungo.
You little shits!
Sizi küçük piçler!
Night after night, he'd roam the streets setting fires,
Her gece, sokaklarda gezer etrafı ateşe verirmiş...
but he'd bribe officials to avoid punishment.
ama yetkililere rüşvet verip cezadan sıyrılırmış.
An arsonist?!
Kundakçı yani?!
Why would he bribe anyone to commit arson?
Yaptığı şeyle eline ne geçiyor ki?
Someone else was profiting from those fires.
Bu yangınlardan başkaları çıkar sağlıyordu.
Enter the man who sold the wood for rebuilding those houses:
O kişi, evleri yeniden inşa etmek için odunları temin eden adam:
That would be Bongo.
Kereste satıcısı, Bongo.
– What?!
– Ne?!
That's not all.
Hepsi bu kadarla bitmiyor.
Yet another targeted those who mourned the loss of family in the fires,
Bir diğeri ise yangınlarda yakınlarını kaybedenlerin acısına göz dikip...
extorting large sums of money from them.
onlardan zorla büyük paralar koparmış...
Meet Bingo, a priest and undertaker.
bir rahip ve cenaze işlerine bakan, Bingo.
No! So those three...
Hadi canım! O zaman bu üçü...
That's right. Bingoh, Bongoh, and Bungoh were in cahoots.
Evet. Bingo, Bongo ve Bungo işbirliği içindeymişler.
I knew it.
Tahmin etmiştim.
They're horrible!
Adiler!
You're not wrong. But no matter what evil they committed,
Aynen öyle. Ne kötülük yaparsa yapsınlar...
they'd buy off officials to avoid any charges.
yetkilileri hep satın almışlar ki tüm suçlamalardan sıyrılabilsinler.
They'd put on a good face in public,
Topluma iyi ve saygılı bir yüz sundular...
but they're actually the worst kind of people.
ama aslında hepsi düpedüz birer alçakmış.
But here's the thing.
Ama olay şu ki...
Interestingly enough, Oiran Komurasaki, that beautiful girl who died yesterday,
ilginçtir, dün ölen güzel kız Oiran Komurasaki...
had the three of them smitten.
üçünün de ağzına sıçmıştı.
All three spent so much money on her that they went broke!
Kıza o kadar çok para yedirdiler ki sonunda iflas ettiler!
The gods were watching after all! And them's the rumors!
Ne ekersen onu biçersin! Tabii hepsi birer söylenti!
That's a good story.
Güzel hikayeymiş.
But... aren't those rumors a bit too specific?
Söylentilere göre fazla detay içermiyor mu?
It's all true, isn't it?
Hepsi doğru, değil mi?
If so, that means the oiran tricked them on purpose!
Öyleyse Oiran onları kasten dolandırmış diyebiliriz!
Impressive.
Etkileyici!
Who was Komurasaki really?
Komurasaki gerçekte kimdi ki?
Hey, those are the guys!
Hey, bunlar onlar!
That's right! I saw them!
Bu doğru! Şimdi hatırladım!
They made a scene during the oiran's procession.
Oiran'ın geçit töreni sırasında olay çıkarmışlardı.
Yasu took them in and provided a place for them to live,
Yasu-san onları kabul etti ve yaşamaları için onlara bir ev verdi...
but they're still acting all high and mighty.
ama hâlâ öfkeli ve saldırgan davranıyorlar.
Tonoyasu really likes taking care of others. Even jerks like them!
Tonoyasu başkalarına yardım etmeyi gerçekten seviyor. Pislik olsalar bile!
I'm certain this symbol inspired a great many people!
Bu sembolün pek çok insana ilham verdiğinden eminim!
Be sure to tell young Kin'emon and the others:
Kin'emon-kun ve diğerlerine mutlaka bu mesajımı iletin:
We'll fight alongside you no matter what!
Zamanı geldiğinde savaşmaya hazır olacağız.
Young Kin'emon?!
Kin'emon-kun mu?!
It brought me joy to see you two again!
İkinizi tekrar görmek bana büyük mutluluk verdi!
Now, it's time to get to work!
Neyse, yapacak çok işim var!
Hey, wait!
Hey, ihtiyar!
You know, lots of people will die in the week leading up to the great battle!
Sonuçta, büyük savaş öncesi pek çok insanın ölmesi de muhtemel!
So if you'll excuse me!
Haydi bana müsaade!
The ladies' man!
Bayanların gözdesi!
The classy dame!
Şık kadın!
And the girl next door!
Ve komşu kızı!
It was good to see you all!
Hepinizi görmek güzeldi!
So, who was that old man?
Eee, kimdi bu ihtiyar?
I listened in but didn't quite catch what his relationship is with you two.
Her şeyi duydum ama sizinle alakasını tam çözemedim.
Ditto.
Keza ben de.
Yes, Tonoyasu's really friendly. But who is he?
Evet. Tonayasu gerçekten dost canlısı. Ama kim o?
The two of us...
İkimizin de...
...have no idea!
zerre fikri yok!
You have no idea?!
Ne demek yok?!
You kept talking to him without knowing who he is?!
Kim olduğunu bilmeden sohbete devam mı ettiniz?
Well, he just kept going on and on...
Şey, adam susmak bilmedi ki...
How could anyone forget such a quirky guy?!
Böyle antika bir adamı kim unutabilir ki?!
He addressed us as "young Kanjuro" and "little Shinobu,"
Bize "kun" ve "chan" kullanarak hitap etti...
so I thought it rude to ask if he had once been someone important.
bu yüzden ona kim olduğunu sormanın kabalık olacağını düşündüm.
He was so casual, so perhaps he's a childhood friend?
Çok samimiydi belki de bir çocukluk arkadaşıdır?
Or a teacher? An older schoolmate maybe?
Yoksa hocanız mı? Belki de okuldan bir ağabey?
Who is he?!
Kimdi lan o?!
– What?!
– Ne?!
You bastards!
Sizi piçler!
Get 'em, Madilloman!
Hakla onları, Madillo Adam!
Hold tight, gramps!
Sıkı tutun, ihtiyar!
You call it haki, but in Wano we refer to it as ryuo.
Sizin haki dediğiniz şey Wano'da ryuo olarak biliniyor.
"Ryuo"...?
"Ryuo" mu?
RYUO
RYUO
It means "to flow."
"Akış" anlamına geliyor.
I imagine your haki flows through your body, too.
Haki de vücudunuzun içinden akıyor olmalı.
You must first feel that flow.
O akışı hissediyor olmalısın.
Alright!
Pekâlâ!
The haki flows through me...
Hakinin akışını hisset...
Don't force it!
Kendini zorlama!
Damn! That's not it!
Kahretsin! Bu değil!
Don't strain yourself!
Bunu zorlayarak yapamazsın.
Allow the unused haki in your body to flow to your fist!
Bedenindeki o atıl hakiyi yumruğuna akıtmalısın!
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka!
You're a goner!
Seni bitireceğim!
That's not it!
Bu değil!
That's not it, either!
Bu da değil!
Damn!
Kahretsin!
That's not it! That's not it!
Bu değil! Değil!
Dammit! Where is it?!
Sıçayım! Nerede bu...
My haki!
hakim?!
It won't flow into my fist!
Yumruklarıma doğru akmıyor!
Hey, hey, he took down too many of my men, that idiot.
Hey, hey... Bayağı adamımı harcadı, salak herif.
Damn!
Kahretsin!
Haki won't flow to an angry fist!
Öfke dolu yumruklar hakiyi yönlendirmez.
Come on! Who's next?!
Sıradaki kim?
Bring it on!
Getirin!
Hey there, gramps! How's the abdominal pain?
Hey büyükbaba! Karın ağrın nasıl oldu?
Oh, Yasu!
Oh, Yasu-san!
It's not much, but I brought you some millet and water.
Fazla değil ama sana biraz darı ve su getirdim.
They'll give you energy!
Kendine iyi bak!
You're so kindhearted, Yasu.
Çok iyi kalplisin, Yasu-san.
What a compliment! It's a joy to be called "kindhearted"!
Ne güzel iltifat ettin! "İyi kalpli" diye anılmak beni çok mutlu etti!
I'll give you two more millet grains!
İşte iki darı tanesi daha!
See you, gramps!
Görüşürüz, büyükbaba!
Hey, it's the granny who sells the seaweed! Do you have enough medicine?
Hey, yosun satan teyze! İlacın var mı, yetiyor mu?
I'm all out, but I feel better already, having seen your face.
Hayır, bitti ama seni gördüğüm için daha iyi hissediyorum.
You're such a man-killer!
Flörte bak!
Oh! Mister, how's the knee?
Ah! Bayım, dizlerin nasıl?
Come play with me, Yasu!
Yasu-san! Benimle oynayın!
Hanko, is your mother getting any better?
Hanko, annen nasıl oldu?
Osaki, how's the baby?
Osaki-san, bebeğin nasıl?
Coochy-coo!
Agucuk gugucuk!
Yasu!
Yasu-san!
Visit with us, too!
Bize de ziyarete gelin!
Here, everyone! Take these!
Pekâlâ, miilet! Herkes gelip alsın!
Thanks again!
Tekrardan teşekkürler!
That Tonoyasu looks to be rolling in dough.
Şu Tonoyasu ne kadar cömert bir adam.
No one else is able to hand out food like that.
Böyle erzak dağıtmak herkesin harcı değil.
It's not what you think.
Düşündüğün gibi değil.
He gets paid peanuts for the work he does.
Yaptığı işe karşılık çerez parası alıyor.
– Peanuts?
– Ne?
His only daughter Toko got sold to the capital and has worked there ever since.
Biricik kızı Toko-chan başkente satıldı ve o günden beri orada çalışıyor.
She sends most of her earnings to Yasu.
Kızı kazancının çoğunu Yasu'ya yolluyor.
Toko?
Toko mu?
I'm not a man!
Ben erkek değilim!
Oh, her!
Ah, o!
Toko-chan sends him money,
Toko-chan kendisine para yolluyor ama o,
but he believes keeping it to himself is a waste.
parayı kendine saklamayı israf sayıyor.
Every day he hands out food to those who can't work,
Kendi boğazından kısıp her gün yardıma muhtaçlara...
though he barely eats anything himself.
erzak dağıtıyor.
He may look ridiculous, but he's a long-beloved figure in our community.
Palyaço gibi davransa da topluluğumuzda eskiden beri çok sevilir.
He's a saint.
O bizim azizimiz.
Daddy...
Babacığım...
Daddy!
Babacığım!
It's bedtime! Go to sleep!
Işıkları kapatın! Derhal uykuya!
Damn!
Kahretsin!
We gotta wait until tomorrow?!
Yarına kadar beklemek zorunda mıyız?!
Let me fight some more!
Daha fazla dövüşmeme izin verin!
So hungry...
Çok açım...
You gonna feed me or what?!
Yoksa beni beslemeyecek misiniz?!
Look at him, barking like some dog.
Şuna bak, tıpkı bir köpek gibi havlıyor.
Shut up and sleep!
Kapa çeneni ve uyu!
I'll be a mummy by tomorrow!
Yarına kalmaz mumyaya dönerim!
May I ask you something, Sir Straw Hat?
Bir şey sorabilir miyim, Bay Hasır Şapka?
What?
Sor!
Why would you want to fight Kaido? I heard that you lost to him in Kuri.
Neden Kaido ile dövüşmek istiyorsun? Kuri'de ona fena yenildiğini duymuştum.
These guys are annoying.
Asabımı bozuyorlar.
Alright, we're good now.
Pekâlâ, şimdi iyiyiz.
Gramps!
İhtiyar...
Have you heard of the Four Emperors?
Yonko'yu hiç duydun mu?
No...
Duymadım...
There are four great pirates called Emperors are in this world...
Yonko olarak bilinen dört korsan, dünyanın denizlerinde seyir hâlindedir.
and Kaido is one of them.
Kaido da onlardan biri.
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates...
Korsanlar Kralı olacağım için...
so I gotta take them all down!
dördünü de indirmem gerek.
The King of the Pirates?
Korsanlar Kralı mı?
Wasn't Roger one such man?
Roger denen adam gibi mi?
You know Gold Roger?!
Gold Roger'ı biliyor musun?!
Yes, from when he came to this country many years ago.
Evet, yıllar önce bu ülkeye geldiğinden biliyorum.
Oh, Kin'emon said the same thing.
Ah, Kin'emon da aynısını söylemişti.
What?! Kin'emon?!
Ne?! Kin'emon mu?!
How do you know that name?!
O ismi nereden biliyorsun?!
What's going on?!
Neler oluyor?!
What?!
Ne?!
You're... R-Raizo!
Sen... R-Raizo'sun!
Straw Hat...
Hasır Şapka-san...
You're...
Sen...
This is Raizo... isn't it?
Raizo... değil misin?
It is I!
Ta kendisiyim!
– What?!
– Ne?!
What's going on with you two?!
Sizin derdiniz ne be?!
How are you still alive,
Nasıl hayatta olabilirsin,
Raizo?!
Raizo?!
Allow me to explain, Boss Hyogoro.
Açıklamama izin verin, Hyogoro-dono!
– Arrest him!
– Tutuklayın onu!
There he is! It's the Witching Hour Boy!
İşte orada! İblis Saati Çocuğu!
Give it up!
Teslim ol!
Seize him!
Yakalayın onu!
So that's the truth, Raizo?!
Öyle mi, Raizo?
It's hard to believe that you are the Boss Hyogoro...!
Sizin o meşhur Hyogoro-dono olduğunuza inanmak güç..!
This is difficult to fathom.
Akıl alır gibi değil.
You are saying you actually crossed through twenty years in time
Yani Wano tarihinin o kara gününden,
from that fateful day in Wano's history?
20 yıl sonrasına mı geçtiniz?
That is correct. It was due to Lady Toki's sorcery.
Aynen öyle. Toki-sama'nın büyüsüydü.
I can't believe it!
Buna inanamıyorum.
I can't believe you, Caribou!
Sana inanamıyorum, Caribou!
Oh, don't say that, Straw Hat!
Ah, böyle konuşma, Hasır Şapka-san!
What the hell, Raizo?!
Neler oluyor, Raizo?!
You thought you had the keys to my cuffs, but they were actually to his!
Kelepçelerimin sandığın anahtarlar aslında onun muymuş?!
All this hate doesn't suit you.
Tüm bu nefret sana hiç yakışmıyor.
Surely I can help in some way.
Eminim sana bir şekilde faydam dokunur.
From now on, I'm your underling!
Bundan sonra askerinim.
But, in exchange...
Ve karşılığı olarak...
please let me leave with you on your ship.
lütfen geminle buradan ayrılmama izin ver.
Ah, so you can't get home?
Ne, yani eve mi dönemiyorsun?
Please forgive me for my past misdeeds!
Lütfen geçmişteki hatalarım için beni affet!
I'm a changed man!
Artık değiştim!
Alright. If you've changed, then it's fine.
Pekâlâ. Madem değiştiğini söylüyorsun, sorun yok.
What?!
Ne?!
Ah, I mean, thank you very much!
Ah, yani çok teşekkür ederim!
Is this some kind of trap?! It scares me how easy that was!
Tuzak falan olmasın?! Bu kadar kolay olmasını beklemiyordum.
Sir Luffytaro, this man uses quite the fascinating sorcery.
Luffytaro-dono, bu adam hayli enteresan bir büyü kullanıyor.
He could be useful.
İşimize yarayabilir.
I never knew when to let go...
Daha ne kadar dayanabilirdim bilmiyorum...
stubbornly clinging to life...
İnatla hayata tutunuyordum...
but it was worth it.
ama buna değdi.
Boss Hyogoro!
Hyogoro-dono!
I was a hair's breadth away.
Ramak kalmıştı.
I thought I'd die a miserable death here...
Burada öleceğimi sandım!
I had made peace with that.
Bunu kabullenmiştim.
If not for your timely arrival, I would have died...
Tam zamanında yetişmeseydin, her şeyden bihaber...
ignorant of everything.
ölüp gidecektim.
The Red Scabbards yet live?
Kızıl Kınlar hâlâ yaşıyor mu?
Oden's child, Kozuki Momonosuke, survived?
Oden'in varisi, Kozuki Momonosuke, hayatta mı?
The fires of rebellion...
Henüz isyan ateşi...
Do they continue to burn?!
sönmemiş demek.
Raizo! Sir Straw Hat!
Raizo! Bay Hasır Şapka!
When it comes to this, even a dotard like me still can contribute!
İş bu raddeye geldiyse, benim gibi bir bunak bile hâlâ işe yarayabilir!
It would be an honor to join you!
Size katılmak benim için onurdur!
Oh, this is an unexpected boon!
Ah, bu beklenmedik bir nimet.
Sir Luffy, this man was once the most highly regarded yakuza in all of Wano!
Luffy-dono, bu adam bir zamanlar Wano'daki tüm yakuzaların patronuydu.
Really?! So you were a big deal back in the day, gramps!
Hadi ya?! Demek eskilerdensin he, ihtiyar!
You mentioned that you have been gathering allies in the Flower Capital?
Çiçek Başkenti'nde müttefik topladığınızdan mı bahsettiniz?
Indeed.
Aynen.
It must have been fate that brought you here to Udon.
Seni buraya, Udon'a getiren kader olsa gerek.
In this labor camp, there are four adjoining mining sites of a similar size to this one.
Buna benzer büyüklükte bitişik dört tutsak madeni daha var.
Tens of thousands of prisoners are being held here in Udon!
Udon'da on binlerce tutsak var!
However, not all of them were arrested for theft or violence.
Ancak çoğu hırsızlık veya şiddet nedeniyle tutuklanmadı.
Most of the prisoners are here for one thing:
Bu madenlerdeki mahkumların çoğu tek bir şeyden suçlu:
treason against Orochi!
Orochi'ye ihanet!
Is that so?! That was an oversight!
Öyle mi?! Bu nasıl bir gaflet!
The country's rage has been pooled into this location!
Ülkenin tüm gazabı bu noktada birikti!
The yakuza bosses who once supported Wano from the shadows are all here.
Bir zamanlar Wano'yu gölgelerden destekleyen yakuza patronlarının hepsi burada.
I will speak with them. They will gladly fight for the Kozuki Clan.
Onlarla konuşacağım. Kozuki Hanesi için memnuniyetle savaşırlar.
Also, Raizo, see that cell?
Ayrıca Raizo, şu hücreyi görüyor musun?
I am already aware.
Biliyorum.
I briefly spoke with Kawamatsu. I intend to release him first.
Kawamatsu ile konuştum. Önceliğim onu serbest bırakmak.
I got it.
Anlaşıldı.
If we smash this place to pieces,
Yani burayı yerle bir edersek...
everyone will join our cause?!
herkes bize mi katılacak?!
Sir Luffy, you are too loud! It will not be that simple!
Luffy-dono, çok bağırıyorsun! Söylediğin kadar kolay değil!
Alright! With that decided, bring us some food!
Pekâlâ! Kararlar alındığına göre bize biraz yiyecek getirin!
Please...
Lütfen...
feed me.
beni besleyin.
I'm hungry... and sleepy.
Çok açım... ve yorgunum.
Are we close to the oshiruko, Okiku?
Oshiruko'ya yaklaştık mı, Okiku-chan?
The sharkodile is also exhausted, but we have already reached Udon.
Timsah köpekbalığı da tükenmiş vaziyette ama zaten Udon'a ulaştık.
Udon Wilderness
Udon- Çorak Topraklar
Wait for me,
Bekle beni...
my sweet oshiruko!
benim tatlı oshiruko'm!
Is it okay that we're here?
Burada olmamız doğru mu?
Oh, it's good!
Ah, harika geldi!
Another bowl!
Bir kase daha!
Oshiruko!
Oshiruko!
Extra! Extra! Breaking news!
Yazıyor! Yazıyor!
The great thief of the Flower Capital,
Çiçek Başkenti'ndeki kargaşanın nedeni...
Flower Capital
Çiçek Başkenti
the troublesome Witching Hour Boy,
İblisa Saati Çocuğu olarak bilinen hırsız...
has finally been caught!
sonunda yakalandı!
Shogun Orochi!
Orochi-sama.
My lord, I have some news you should hear.
Orochi-sama, bilmeniz gereken bazı haberlerim var.
It is about the Witching Hour Boy, who was apprehended the other day.
Geçen gün tutuklanan İblis Saati Çocuğu'yla ilgili.
Be silent!
Kes sesini!
Have you no sense of how I feel, having lost the love of my life?!
Hayatımın aşkını kaybettiğim için nasıl hissettiğimi bilmiyor musun?
I have only the deepest of sympathies for the passing of Oiran Komurasaki...
Oiran Komurasaki'nin ölümü beni derinden üzdü.
But with all due respect, my lord...
Ama tüm saygımla efendim...
Kyoshiro's decision was most prudent.
Kyoshiro'nun kararı son derece ihtiyatlıydı.
If we let anyone who opposes the shogun live,
Şoguna karşı çıkan herkesin yaşamasına izin verirsek...
it could undermine His Excellency's authority and prestige.
bu, ekselanslarının otoritesini ve prestijini mahvedebilir.
My lord...!
Orochi-sama!
I couldn't care less about the Witching Hour Boy...
İblis Saati Çocuğu umurumda değil!
Komurasaki... No other woman could match her beauty.
Komurasaki... Başka hiçbir kadın onun güzelliğiyle yarışamaz.
Do you not understand that?!
Bunu anlayamıyor musun?!
Thank you for the honor of your presence, Shogun Orochi.
Varlığınızla beni onurlandırdığınız için teşekkür ediyorum, Orochi-sama.
But I beg you, please hear me out.
Ama size yalvarıyorum, lütfen dinleyin.
The Witching Hour Boy was not your run-of-the-mill thief.
İblisa Saati Çocuğu, sıradan bir hırsız değilmiş.
He was a cowardly burglar who wreaked havoc throughout the Flower Capital.
Çiçek Başkenti'ni kasıp kavuran sinsi bir suçluydu o.
He stole from the rich and gave to the poor,
Çaldığı parayı fakirlere dağıtıp kahramanca niyetleri olan...
becoming a petty villain with heroic intentions.
küçük bir kötü adam hâline geldi.
He is currently in custody at Rasetsu Prison.
Şu anda Rasetsu Hapishanesi'nde.
His true identity is...
Gerçek kimliği...
What?!
Ne?!
It's him!
O!
H-He... lives?!
O-O... yaşıyor mu?!
No! I cannot believe it!
Hayır! Buna inanamıyorum!
It's him!
O!
You are of the Kurozumi Clan? Why did you hide it?
Kurozumi Hanesi'nden misin? Neden bunu sakladın?
It's him! It's him!
Bu o! Bu o!
My lord? My lord?!
Efendim? Efendim?!
What shall we do about the Witching Hour Boy?
Onun hakkında kararınız nedir?
Isn't it obvious?!
Çok bariz değil mi?!
Execute him! Make a public example out of him!
İnfaz edin onu! Halka örnek olsun!
Illuminate the light scrolls across Wano immediately!
İnfazı Wano'nun her yerinde hemen yayınlayın!
They already stand at the ready.
Görüntü yansıtıcılar kuruldu bile.
Kyoshiro!
Kyoshiro!
Today, Komurasaki's public funeral will also take place in the capital.
Bugün başkentte, Komurasaki'nin halka açık cenaze töreni de düzenlenecek.
Large, grieving crowds hold the potential for disorderly conduct...
Bu kadar büyük ve kederli kalabalıklar düzensiz davranış potansiyeli taşır...
so I have made preparations.
bu yüzden bir kaç hazırlık yaptım.
That's my Kyoshiro!
Aslanım Kyoshiro be!
What are your orders, my lord?
Emirleriniz nelerdir, efendim?
I've made up my mind.
Kararımı verdim.
We will have the Witching Hour Boy join Komurasaki in death.
İblis Saati Çocuğu'nu, öbür dünyada Komurasaki ile kavuşturacağız.
He'll be an offering at Komurasaki's funeral!
Komurasaki'nin cenazesine adak olacak!
Yes, my lord.
Başüstüne.
It's sadly poetic to have the capital's two biggest stars share the stage in death!
Başkentin en büyük iki yıldızının ölüme birlikte yürümesi, kaderin acı bir cilvesi adeta!
That is exactly the stroke of genius I expect of my shogun.
Bu tam da şogunumuza yaraşır dahiyane bir fikir.
I, too, will attend.
Ben de katılacağım.
I will witness his execution to the end! I need a palanquin now!
Bunu kaçıramam! Tahtırevan'ımı hazırlayın!
Udon's Prisoner Mining Camp
Udon- Tutsak Madeni
It can't be!
Bu olamaz!
I can't deal with these bad jokes in the morning, Kaido.
Sabah sabah bu berbat şakaları hiç çekemem, Kaido-san.
It's not a joke.
Şaka değil.
No... It can't be!
Hayır... olamaz!
If you don't believe me, connect a light-scroll snail and see for yourself!
İnanmıyorsan görüntü yansıtıcıyı bağla ve kendin gör!
No!
Hayır!
My Komurasaki!
Komurasaki-tan!
Hey!
Hey!
Huh?
Ha?
He found out Komurasaki died.
Komurasaki'nin öldüğünü öğrendi.
Queen's gonna be in a bad mood for a while.
Queen-sama, bir süreliğine berbat hâlde olacak.
This is bad. What should we do?
Bu hiç iyi olmadı. Ne yapacağız?
Hey, balloon!
Hey, balon!
Hurry and get out here!
Çabuk ol ve çık artık şuradan!
Shut up! I don't have time for your nonsense!
Kapa' çeneni! Saçmalıklarına ayıracak vaktim yok!
Hey, balloon! When are we gonna start today's sumo match?
Hey, balon! Bugünün müsabakası ne zaman başlayacak?
Don't waste my time!
Zamanımı boşa harcama!
Did you guys get fat overnight or something?!
Sizler bir gecede nasıl bu kadar şişmanladınız?!
No, we didn't! It's just your imagination!
Öyle bir şey yok! Hayal görüyor olmalısın!
O-Oh. I see.
A-Ah. Anladım.
Hey, do we report that the red bean soup vanished overnight?
Hey, oshiruko'nun gece buhar olup uçtuğunu rapor edecek miyiz?
Anyway, that's not important right now!
Unut gitsin!
No way! What would Queen do if he heard more bad news?!
Saçmalama! Daha fazla kötü haber duyarsa Queen-sama ortalığı yıkar!
Good point.
Haklısın.
But I wonder where the red-bean soup went...
Ama oshiruko hangi cehenneme kayboldu?
This is precisely why I warned Sir Luffy not to eat too much...
Çok fazla yerse fark edileceği konusunda Luffy-dono'yu uyarmıştım.
Eating every last drop of oshiruko soup was just excessive!
Oshiruko'nun hepsini silip süpürerek işin cılkını çıkardılar!
How does an idiot like him stay alive?
Böyle bir salak nasıl oluyor da hâlâ yaşıyor?
More importantly, it's sumo time! Sumo!
Hadi şu sumo maçını yapalım artık!
Let's go! Dosukoi!
Hadi! Dosukoi!
I don't have time for idiots. I gotta know the truth!
Aptallarla uğraşacak vaktim yok. Gerçeği öğrenmem gerekiyor!
Hey, get me a video feed of the Flower Capital now!
Hey, çabuk Çiçek Başkenti yayınına bağlayın beni!
Ready the light-scroll snail!
Görüntü yansıtıcıyı hazır edin!
The light-scroll snail is set!
Görüntü yansıtıcı hazır!
Show me the Flower Capital.
Bana Çiçek Başkenti'ni gösterin.
A video transponder snail?
Görüntü yansıtan salyangoz mu?
What? So that's the Flower Capital.
Ne? Çiçek Başkenti'ni gösteriyor.
Mount Atama, Kuri
Atama Dağı, Kuri
Mount Atama Thieves,
Atama Dağı Hırsızları...
how dare you scum steal all of my food and weapons!
silahlarımı ve erzaklarımı çalmaya nasıl cesaret edersiniz?!
Let's settle this here and now!
Hesabızı hemen şuracıkta keseceğim!
I'll give you a taste of my trick sword!
Size hileli kılıcımı bir tattırayım!
I'll devastate Mount Atama!
Atama Dağı'nı yıkacağım!
This is the end of the Mount Atama Thieves.
Siz Atama Dağı Hırsızları'nın sonunu getireceğim.
It's too late! The fire is spreading fast!
Çok geç! Yangın çok hızlı yayılıyor!
There's no extinguishing it, Shutenmaru!
Söndürmenin imkânı yok, Shutenmaru-san!
That bastard Holdem!
Şerefsiz, Holdem!
Head to Bakura Town!
Bakura Kasabası'na ilerleyin!
Bakura Town?! We'll have to contend with Kaido's forces!
Bakura Kasabası mı?! Ama Kaido'nun güçleri orada!
So what?!
Ee, ne olmuş?!
I'll crush them all!
Hepsini paramparça edeceğim!
An Abandoned Village in Kuri
Kuri- Terkedilmiş bir Köy
I see. I feel sorry for what is happening to Ashura Doji.
Anlıyorum. Ashura Doji'nin başına gelenleri duymak çok üzücü.
Mm-hm... But we did it for the greater good.
Öyle... Ama bunu davanın selameti için yaptık.
It was unavoidable.
Bu kaçınılmazdı.
We'll head to Bakura Town.
Bakura Kasabası'na gidiyoruz.
Our plan was foiled, and we have no solution in sight.
Planımız suya düştü ve görünürde bir çözümümüz yok.
For now, we'll get Ashura to see the Beast Pirates as his enemy.
Şimdilik, Ashura'nın Canavar Korsanları'nı düşmanı olarak görmesini sağlayacağız.
His joining us is crucial to our cause!
Onun bize katılması davamız açısından çok önemli!
Ringo's Northern Cemetery
Ringo- Kuzey Mezarlığı
Here I am... Wh-Wh-What?!
Ben gel... N-N-Ne?!
What?!
Neee?!
Who is this?! What is this?!
Bu kim?! Bu ne?!
Wh-Wh-What's the story here?!
B-Burada neler yaşandı böyle?!
Brook? What's wrong with you? Why are you here? Hm?
Brook? Sorun ne? Neden buradasın? Ha?
Zoro, my eyes are popping out of my skull just seeing you like that!
Zoro, seni böyle görünce gözlerim yerinden fırladı!
I'm a skeleton, though, so having eyes isn't really my thing!
Gerçi ben bir iskeletim, yani gözlerim yok!
So sorry for the interruption!
Böldüğüm için özür dilerim.
Hey, don't get the wrong idea! Get back in here!
Hey, sandığın gibi değil! Buraya gel!
Oh? Well, okay... If it's no trouble, I'd be happy to.
Öyle mi? Şey, peki... Size zahmet olmayacaksa, seve seve.
Wow, I'm smitten!
Vay canına, resmen vuruldum!
If you would be so obliged, may I see your panties?
Müsaadenizle külodunuzu görebilir miyim?
A ghost!
Hayalet!
Wait, he's with me!
Bekle, o benimle!
I'm so hungry... A curse on you!
Çok acıktım. Lanetlendiniz!
How scary!
Çok korkunç!
Kin'emon tasked me with saying that around here.
Kin'emon-san buralarda bunu söylemem için beni görevlendirdi.
Oh, I see.
Ah, anlıyorum.
That's why there are so many offerings out there.
Demek dışarıda bu yüzden o kadar çok adak var.
At any rate, it's hard to believe you're Momonosuke's little sister.
Senin Momonosuke-san'ın küçük kız kardeşi olduğuna inanmak güç.
You're as beautiful as an oiran.
Bir oiran kadar güzelsin.
She sure is. I mean, she is an oiran.
Kesinlikle. Zaten bir oiran.
I'm jealous, Zoro. How'd you get someone like this to tend to you?!
Çok kıskandım, Zoro-san. Böylesini eline düşürmeyi nasıl başardın?!
I just went to sleep. That's all.
Sadece uykuya daldım. Hepsi bu.
I am so sorry. You just looked like you were cold.
Çok üzgünüm. Üşümüş gibi görünüyordun.
Truth be told, everyone gets love-struck lying next to me!
Ne yalan söyleyeyim, yanıma uzanan herkes bana abayı yakıyor!
Did you like it? No, certainly you loved it!
Hoşuna gitti mi? Eminim gitmiştir!
Awful straightforward of you...!
Çok açık sözlüsün.
Of course!
Öyleyim!
Anyway, I have no idea where Nami and the others went.
Neyse, Nami-san ve diğerlerinin nereye gittiğine dair hiçbir fikrim yok.
Yesterday, they went to the bathhouse,
Dün hamama gitmişlerdi,
but they weren't there when I went to meet them.
ama oraya gittiğimde onları bulamadım.
Oh, that reminds me. The Flower Capital is in an absolute frenzy.
Ah, aklıma gelmişken. Çiçek Başkenti tam bir kaos içinde.
I heard that today is the funeral for Komurasaki, Wano's most beautiful oiran.
Bugün, Wano'nun en güzel oiran'ı Komurasaki'nin cenaze töreni olduğunu duydum.
Plus, they caught the Witching Hour Boy, the master thief who shared his spoils with the poor!
Üstelik ganimetlerini fakirlerle paylaşan usta hırsız, İblis Saati Çocuğu'nu da yakalamışlar!
That news is causing a fuss too!
O haber de büyük yaygara kopardı!
Ther Witching Hour Boy?! But he couldn't have!
İblis Saati Çocuğu mu?! Emin misin?!
But it's true.
Evet, eminim.
Look, it's right here on this broadsheet.
Bakın, bugünün ekstra baskısı.
It says that he will be executed in the capital today. They even discovered his true identity.
Bugün başkentte idam edileceği yazıyor. Hatta gerçek kimliğini de ortaya çıkardılar.
He seems to be well known in Ebisu Town...
Görünüşe göre Ebisu Kasabası'nda ünlü birisiymiş.
You said Ebisu Town?!
Ebisu Kasabası mı?
Yes, his name was something like...
Evet, adı...
I'm fairly sure it was something like Yasu...
Yasu gibi bir şeydi.
Tonoyasu?!
Tonoyasu mu?!
Ah, yes, that's him.
Ah, evet, o.
Toko!
Toko!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Hey, sorun ne?!
Wait, Toko!
Bekle, Toko!
Thank you for yesterday. I will be forever in your debt.
Dün için teşekkürler. İyiliğini asla unutmayacağız!
Wait, you idiot!
Bekle, seni sersem!
You couldn't even protect her yesterday!
Onu tek başına koruyamazsın!
Whaaat?! I only just made it back here!
Neee?! Başkentten daha yeni döndüm ama!
Wait for me! Hey, you guys!
Beni bekleyin! Hey, size diyorum!
Daddy...
Babacığım...
Hey, get up.
Hey, kalk.
You're here to escort me? How nice of you...
Benim için mi geldiniz? Çok naziksiniz.
It... It can't be.
Bu... Bu olamaz.
He looks like...
Şeye çok benziyor...
Where are you going?! They want your head!
Nereye gidiyorsun?! Hayatın tehlikede!
Let me go! I need to go!
Bırak beni! Gitmem gerekiyor!
Hey, pull it together!
Hey, sakinleş!
Let me go!
Bırak beni!
What's going on?!
Onun nesi var?!
Toko!
Toko!
They're gonna execute him!
Onu idam edecekler!
Let me go!
Bırak beni!
They're gonna kill him!
Onu öldürecekler!
He's my daddy!
O benim babam!
Toko...
Toko...
What'd you say?!
Ne dedin sen?!
Looks like another beautiful day in the Flower Capital...
Desenize, Çiçek Başkenti'nde yine harika bir gün olacak...